<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>6. Pneumatics on FRC Zero</title>
    <link>https://frczero.org/pneumatics/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 6. Pneumatics on FRC Zero</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 04 Feb 2023 22:28:37 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://frczero.org/pneumatics/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>6.1 What are Pneumatics?</title>
      <link>https://frczero.org/pneumatics/what-are-pneumatics/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Feb 2023 22:27:39 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://frczero.org/pneumatics/what-are-pneumatics/</guid>
      <description>Originally discovered by the ancient Greeks, pneumatics is the study of air pressure. Pneumatics is a branch of fluid power that uses compressed air to power actuators. Pneumatic actuators are used to move mechanical parts, such as valves, cylinders, and other devices. Pneumatic systems are used in a wide variety of applications, including robotics, manufacturing, and construction.
In FRC teams typically use cylinders to extend and retract a piston. This can be used to move a mechanism in a linear direction, or to rotate a mechanism.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>6.2 What are Pneumatic Components?</title>
      <link>https://frczero.org/pneumatics/pneumatic-components/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Feb 2023 22:27:39 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://frczero.org/pneumatics/pneumatic-components/</guid>
      <description>Pneumatic components are the parts of a pneumatic system that use compressed air to do work. There are many different types of pneumatic components. The most common pneumatic components are shown in the table below:
Component Description Image Vendor Link(s) Solenoid A solenoid is a valve that uses an electric current to open and close. It is used to control the flow of air in a pneumatic system. Solenoids can be 12v or 24v.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>6.3 Pneumatic Safety</title>
      <link>https://frczero.org/pneumatics/pneumatic-safety/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Feb 2023 22:27:39 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://frczero.org/pneumatics/pneumatic-safety/</guid>
      <description>Pneumatics are powerful and can be dangerous if not used properly. This section will cover the safety rules and guidelines for pneumatics. As is the case with all safety rules, they are not meant to be restrictive. They are meant to be guidelines to help keep you safe. If you have any questions about the safety rules, please ask your mentor or coach.
Safety Rules Never use compressed air to propel a projectile.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>6.4 How to Setup a Pneumatic System</title>
      <link>https://frczero.org/pneumatics/pneumatic-systems/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Feb 2023 22:27:39 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://frczero.org/pneumatics/pneumatic-systems/</guid>
      <description>Setting up a pneumatic system can be a daunting task. This section will cover the basics of setting up a pneumatic system. It will cover the basics of the components and how to connect them. It will also cover the basics of how to setup the compressor and the PCM and how to test the system.
Gatherings the Components The first step in setting up a pneumatic system is to gather the components.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>6.5 Pneumatic Control</title>
      <link>https://frczero.org/pneumatics/pneumatic-control/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Feb 2023 22:27:39 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://frczero.org/pneumatics/pneumatic-control/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>6.6 Pneumatic Troubleshooting</title>
      <link>https://frczero.org/pneumatics/pneumatic-troubleshooting/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Feb 2023 22:27:39 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://frczero.org/pneumatics/pneumatic-troubleshooting/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>6.7 Pneumatic Resources</title>
      <link>https://frczero.org/pneumatics/pneumatic-resources/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Feb 2023 22:27:39 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://frczero.org/pneumatics/pneumatic-resources/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
