<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>2.1 Design Process on FRC Zero</title>
    <link>https://frczero.org/engineering_design/design_process/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 2.1 Design Process on FRC Zero</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://frczero.org/engineering_design/design_process/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>2.1.1 Identify the Problem</title>
      <link>https://frczero.org/engineering_design/design_process/identify_the_problem/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://frczero.org/engineering_design/design_process/identify_the_problem/</guid>
      <description>The first step in the design process is to identify the problem. This is the most important step in the process. If you don&amp;rsquo;t know what the problem is, you can&amp;rsquo;t solve it. The problem should be clearly defined. It should be specific, and not too broad. It should also be measurable. This means that you should be able to know when the problem is solved. For example, if the problem is &amp;ldquo;I want to build a robot that can score points in the game&amp;rdquo;, that is too broad.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2.1.2 Research the Problem</title>
      <link>https://frczero.org/engineering_design/design_process/research_the_problem/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://frczero.org/engineering_design/design_process/research_the_problem/</guid>
      <description>Now that you know what the problem is, you can work towards solving it. Before reinventing the wheel and 3D printing it&amp;hellip; The best way to solve a problem is to find someone who has already solved it. This is called research. While this is not always possible, it is a good idea to try and find an existing solution. If you can&amp;rsquo;t find an existing solution, you can use the research to help you brainstorm a new solution.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2.1.3 Brainstorming Ideas</title>
      <link>https://frczero.org/engineering_design/design_process/brainstorming_ideas/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://frczero.org/engineering_design/design_process/brainstorming_ideas/</guid>
      <description>Brainstorming is the process of generating as many ideas as possible. This can and should be a fun process. The ideas do not all need to be good, they just need to be different. The more ideas you generate, the more likely you are to find a good idea among the nonsense. While brainstorming, it is important to not judge the ideas and really encourage free thinking. Ideas can be documented in many ways, but no matter what it should be fun and easy to do.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2.1.4 Create a Prototype</title>
      <link>https://frczero.org/engineering_design/design_process/creating_a_prototype/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://frczero.org/engineering_design/design_process/creating_a_prototype/</guid>
      <description>What is a Prototype? A prototype is a model of the final product. It is used to test the design and make sure that it works. A prototype is not the final product. While you could use a prototype as the final product, it is not recommended. On the first attempt at building a prototype, you should not use expensive materials. You should use cheap materials that are easy to work with.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2.1.5 Testing a Prototype</title>
      <link>https://frczero.org/engineering_design/design_process/test_a_prototype/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://frczero.org/engineering_design/design_process/test_a_prototype/</guid>
      <description>Testing the prototype that you created is an important step in the design process. It allows you to make sure that the prototype works as expected. It also allows you to make changes to the prototype early in the design process. This will save you time and money in the long run. Time in the FRC season is very limited, so you should make sure that you are spending your time wisely.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2.1.6 Communicate the Results</title>
      <link>https://frczero.org/engineering_design/design_process/communicate_the_results/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://frczero.org/engineering_design/design_process/communicate_the_results/</guid>
      <description>Why is it important to communicate the results? Communicating the results of the design process is important because it allows you to share your ideas with others. It also allows you to get feedback on your ideas. This feedback can help you improve your design. Communicating the results of the design process is also important because it means you have your data organized in a way that is easy to understand.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2.1.7 Repeat the Design Process</title>
      <link>https://frczero.org/engineering_design/design_process/repeat_the_design_process/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://frczero.org/engineering_design/design_process/repeat_the_design_process/</guid>
      <description>What is iteration? Iteration is the process of repeating a given process over and over again. In the design process, iteration is the process of repeating the design process over and over again for each new problem that is encountered. The design process is cyclical, meaning that it is repeated over and over again. The design process is also iterative, meaning that it is repeated over and over again at any level of the process as needed.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
