<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>8.5 Team Branding on FRC Zero</title>
    <link>https://frczero.org/business_marketing/team_branding/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 8.5 Team Branding on FRC Zero</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 26 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://frczero.org/business_marketing/team_branding/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>8.5.1 What is Team Branding?</title>
      <link>https://frczero.org/business_marketing/team_branding/what-is-team-branding/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://frczero.org/business_marketing/team_branding/what-is-team-branding/</guid>
      <description>What is a Brand? In the context of FRC the team&amp;rsquo;s brand can include its name, logo, and other visual elements. These elements are used to create a consistent look and feel for the team. By planning ahead, creating styling guides and more, the team can create a brand that is easily recognizable and memorable. It&amp;rsquo;s also easy to create new content that fits within the brand.
New members to your business and marketing team can make new content Day one and already have their templates and branding guidelines to follow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>8.5.2 Team Branding Examples</title>
      <link>https://frczero.org/business_marketing/team_branding/team-branding-examples/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://frczero.org/business_marketing/team_branding/team-branding-examples/</guid>
      <description>This section will show you some examples of team branding. We picked teams that we know, or we think are good examples of branding. If you know of a team that has good branding, please let us know and we will add them to this list.
Team 453 - Rockem Sockem Robotics (Author&amp;rsquo;s team) The Team Website was just redone with some of these ideas in mind. The previous website was a bit dated, and the new one is much more modern and easier to update using SSG just like frczero.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>8.5.3 Team Branding Resources</title>
      <link>https://frczero.org/business_marketing/team_branding/team-branding-resources/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://frczero.org/business_marketing/team_branding/team-branding-resources/</guid>
      <description>This section will cover team branding resources. This includes software, websites, and other resources that can be used to create team branding. it also includes resources that can be used to learn more about team branding.
Software &amp;amp; Websites Paint.net Paint.net is a free image and photo editing software for computers that run Windows. It is a great alternative to Adobe Photoshop. It is very similar to Photoshop, but it is much easier to use.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
